Alesia White

Accounting Specialist

Los Angeles, CA 90047 alesiawhitr9_ixc@indeedemail.com (323) 219-1544

Accounting Specialist with over 20 years of experience with a passion to meet deadlines. I'm a team player that enjoys sharing my knowledge and helping others. I'm a fast learner and eager to learn new skills. I'm seeking a challenging career within a stable organization that will allow me to utilize my full potential and enhance my skills.

#readytowork

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Cash Operations Specialist

Sheppard Mullin Richter & Hampton LLP - Los Angeles, CA November 2019 to March 2020

Post clients payments by recording cash, check, credit cards, and bank wire. Post revenues by verifying and entering transactions from lock box and local deposits. Verified and validity any account discrepancies. Entered adjusting entries approved and requested by partners and billing department. Resolve payment deduction by examining clients payment plans, payment history and discounts. Prepare daily cash reports. Assist in month end closing.

Accounts Payable Clerk

Manatt Phelps & Phillips, LL - Los Angeles, CA 2008 to 2019

Responsibilities included processing approximately 500-600

vendor invoices weekly. Responsible for all Legal Library invoices

for nine Manatt offices across the United States. Coded and processed all air travel and transportation expenses us in ing banking

credit card systems. Coded and processed all courier invoices.

Processed Trademark and Transcript invoices. Provided

needed backup for billing department for expenses billed to clients. Review and reconcile vendor statements. Code and

processed all overhead invoices for several Manatt offices.

Receiving and processing invoices via email. Scanning all

documents to provide a paperless environment. Research, code and process all refund and credits. Assist with yearly 1099

preparation. Provided assistance to accounts payable supervisor and accounts payable lead as requested.

Software Programs Used: Aderant Legal Software, Chrome River, Microsoft Word, Excel

Accounts Payable Supervisor

Warren Distribution - Santa Ana, CA 2006 to 2008

Supervisor accounts payable department. Provided support for A department of four employees. Code and processed invoices

for a large auto parts distribution center. Matching invoices with purchase orders for accuracy. Processed payroll using ADP

payroll processing system. Responsible for all company fleet

insurance and registration. Processed and reconcile returns and rebates. Reconcile vendor statements and discrepancies.

Accounting Specialist

MACSTEEL USA - Fontana, CA 2001 to 2006

Responsibilities included processing approximately 300-500 vendor

invoices weekly. Processed the complete accounting cycle for payment of steel and freight invoices for several division throughout the United State.

Reconcile vessel, vendor, and customer accounts. Organized and

maintained confidential accounting records and documents, Worked closely with the purchasing department to assure price and

quantity accuracy. Research disputed accounts receivables. Assist

control with training and cross training new accounts receivable and accounts payable staff.

Education

Associate in Accounting

West Los Angeles College - Culver City, CA 1981 to 1984

Skills

- Payroll
- Data entry
- Excel
- · Microsoft office
- Account reconciliation
- Adp payroll system
- · Accounts Payable
- Accounts Receivable
- AP
- Invoice
- Concur
- Peoplesoft
- Quickbooks

- Accounting
- Office Management
- Bank Reconciliation
- General Ledger Accounting
- Journal Entries
- Forecasting
- Sage
- Auditing
- Tax Experience

Additional Information

Skills

Microsoft Excel Microsoft Office 10 Key

Data Entry Account Reconciliation ADP Payroll System